eyefi.com 2016-06-01

# Privacy Policy | Eyefi

Eyefi

Last Revised Nov. 15, 2015

Eye-Fi, Inc. ("Eyefi") is committed to protecting your privacy and ensuring you have a positive experience on our website and in using our products and services (collectively "Products"). This policy covers the Eyefi websites and applications and is applicable worldwide. This policy outlines our personal information handling practices for both online and offline data. If you give us personal information, we will treat it according to this policy. This policy may be updated from time to time and our website will indicate when the policy has been updated. You may access the current version at any time by clicking on the "Privacy Policy" link at the footer on our website. References to Eyefi in this privacy policy include Eyefi subsidiaries and affiliates.

## Collection of your personal information

Described below are situations in which personal information is collected and the purposes for which it is collected. "Personal Information" is any information that can be used to identify an individual, and may include, but is not limited to, name, email address, postal or other physical address, credit or debit card number, information generated from use of our Products, and other information required to provide a Product, deliver a product, or carry out a transaction you have requested. Personal Information may also include "Content," as defined below. Some of the reasons we collect your Personal Information may include:

  * account registration
  * use of certain Product features
  * generating reports based on information collected from use of our Products
  * requesting service and support for our Products and providing such support
  * placing transactions or orders
  * participating in an online survey
  * submitting an entry for a sweepstakes or other promotion
  * billing and collecting payments for our Products
  * participating in discussion groups or forums
  * registering for membership programs or newsletter subscriptions
  * customizing the advertising and content you see

When you access your Eyefi account and utilize Eyefi services, Eyefi automatically records certain information about your use, such as account activity, data displayed or clicked on, and other information including browser type, IP address, date and time of access, cookie ID, and referrer URL. Some of this information collected, such as IP address and the contents of certain cookies, may include personal information.

## Automated Collection of Information

### Analytics information:

We use third-party analytics tools to help us measure traffic and usage trends for our Products. These tools collect information sent by your device or our Products, including the web pages you visit, add-ons, and other information that assists us in improving the Products. We collect and use this analytics information with analytics information from other Users so that it cannot reasonably be used to identify any particular individual User.

### Log file information:

Log file information is automatically reported by your browser each time you make a request to access (i.e., visit) a web page or app. It can also be provided when the content of the webpage or app is downloaded to your browser or device.

When you use our Products, our servers automatically record certain log file information, including your web request, Internet Protocol ("IP") address, browser type, referring / exit pages and URLs, number of clicks and how you interact with links on the Products, domain names, landing pages, pages viewed, and other such information. We may also collect similar information from emails sent to our Users which then help us track which emails are opened and which links are clicked by recipients. The information allows for more accurate reporting and improvement of the Products.

### Device identifiers:

When you use a mobile device like a tablet or phone to access our Products, we may access, collect, monitor, store on your device, and/or remotely store one or more "device identifiers." Device identifiers are small data files or similar data structures stored on or associated with your mobile device, which uniquely identify your mobile device. A device identifier may be data stored in connection with the device hardware, data stored in connection with the device's operating system or other software, or data sent to the device by the Products.

A device identifier may deliver information to us or to a third party partner about how you browse and use the Products and may help us or others provide reports or personalized content and ads. Some features of the Products may not function properly if use or availability of device identifiers is impaired or disabled.

### Metadata:

Metadata is usually technical data that is associated with Content. For example, Metadata can describe how, when and by whom a piece of Content was collected and how that content is formatted.

Users can add or may have Metadata added to their Content (e.g., to mark keywords when you post a photo), geotag (e.g., to mark your location to a photo), comments or other data. This makes your Content more searchable by others and more interactive. If you geotag your photo or tag your photo using other's APIs then, your latitude and longitude will be stored with the photo and searchable (e.g., through a location or map feature) if your photo is made public by you.

### Cookies:

Like many websites, Eyefi uses technologies, such as cookies and web beacons, which allow us to make your visit to our website easier, more efficient and more valuable by providing you with a customized experience and recognizing you when you return.

A cookie cannot read personal data off your hard disk or read cookie files created by other sites; indeed, the only Personal Information a cookie can contain is information you supply yourself. Accepting the cookies used on our website may give us access to information about your browsing behavior, which we may use to personalize your experience and track user traffic patterns, and to merge this info when you register. We do this in order to determine the usefulness of our website information to our users and to see how effective our navigational structure is in helping users reach that information.

In addition, Eyefi uses web beacons in conjunction with cookies to understand user behavior. Web beacons are simply a convenient way of gathering basic statistics and managing cookies, and do not give away any extra information from your computer. Turning off your browser's cookies will prevent web beacons from tracking your specific activity.

If you prefer not to receive cookies while browsing our website or via HTML-formatted emails, you can set your browser to warn you before it accepts cookies or refuse the cookie when your browser alerts you to its presence. You can also refuse all cookies by turning them off in your browser. Disabling cookies on your computer may cause Eyefi web pages to be inaccessible, inoperable or may disable some features. For additional information about cookies and other tracking technologies, including instructions for blocking their use, see http://privacy.getnetwise.org/browsing/tools.

## Uses of your Personal Information

We will use your Personal Information only in accordance with our Privacy Policy. If you do not wish us to continue using your Personal Information in this manner, you may request that your account be deactivated as specified below. Some of the ways we may use your Personal Information include:

  * To process your orders and provide the Products that you have ordered or obtained.
  * To provide reports based on information collected from use of our Products.
  * To keep you up to date on the latest Product announcements, software updates, software upgrades, system enhancements, special offers, and other information, provided that you can edit your marketing preferences at any time as described below.
  * To provide support and assistance for our Products.
  * To provide the ability to create personal profile areas and view protected content.
  * To provide the ability to contact you, and provide you with shipping and billing information.
  * To provide customer feedback and support.
  * To provide and administer contests, sweepstakes or other marketing or promotional activities.
  * To conduct questionnaires and surveys in order to provide better products and services to our customers and end users. Your completion of any questionnaires is voluntary.
  * To support recruitment inquiries.
  * To understand more about you, so we can personalize newsletters and websites to your preferences. For example, allowing you the opportunity to request specific information on products and services that may be of interest.
  * To provide information, at your request, to another individual such as a friend, family member or co-worker.
  * To meet contract obligations.

## Content

If you transfer photos, videos and related EXIF data (collectively, "Content") directly between Eyefi cards and cameras and other supported devices, which may include computers, smartphones, or tablets, Eyefi does not transfer such Content to, or store such Content on, Eyefi servers. However, when you use many other Product features, such as synchronization, storage, sharing, relayed uploads, hotspot services, and other services we may offer now or in the future, that use often can involve transferring Content to and storing Content on Eyefi servers for access by you and others authorized by you.

Eyefi handles your Content the same as other Personal Information described in this privacy policy.

## Accessing and updating your Personal Information

If you allow Eyefi Products to access your Content or other Personal Information, which you have stored in third party products and services, you will need to manage that Personal Information through your third party accounts. We do not have the ability to modify or delete your Personal Information stored in third party products and services.

If you believe Eyefi is in possession of your Personal Information that you want modified or deleted, you may make changes or delete your account at your discretion, directly through our web site. Or you may send an email request to [privacy@eyefi.com](mailto:privacy@eyefi.com). We may need to retain some Personal Information for the period of time necessary for legal proceedings, legal requirements or for settling your account, and some copies of your Personal Information may remain in our backups.

## Unsubscribing and Opting Out

You may unsubscribe from Eyefi's promotional emails by clicking the "unsubscribe" link at the bottom of any of our promotional emails, or by sending a letter to:

Eyefi  
Attn: Privacy Officer  
967 North Shoreline Blvd,  
Mountain View, CA 94043 USA

From time to time Eyefi will merchandise its products with the use of Internet based advertising companies. These companies will use cookies and other information (but not including your name, address, email address, or telephone number) about your visits to this and other websites in order to provide advertisements for products and services (including those of third parties) which may be of interest to you. If you wish to opt-out from these forms of marketing on (or with respect to your use of) the Eyefi website, please follow the opt-out instructions in the following link: [www.networkadvertising.org/choices/](http://www.networkadvertising.org/choices/)

## Non-personal/anonymous information collection

In some instances, Eyefi may collect non-personal (aggregate or demographic) data through cookies, web logs, and web beacons. This information is used to better understand and improve the usability, performance, and effectiveness of the website. Please read the "Cookies" section below for more information.

In addition, by using some of our Products, anonymous network information may be transmitted back to us such as Product usage information. This information is transmitted back to us so we can determine how users are interacting with our Products, to assist us with improving our Products, and to correct any problems that may occur.

## Sharing your personal information

We do not sell or rent your Personal Information to third parties for marketing purposes unless you have granted us permission to do so.

We may share your Personal Information within Eyefi and with third party service providers for purposes of managing your accounts, providing Products, or assisting in transactions, including processing orders, processing credit card transactions, hosting websites, storing Content, and providing customer support. We only provide these third parties with Personal Information which is necessary to provide or complete the requested Product or transaction, and the third parties are not permitted to use your Personal Information except for limited purpose of providing and completing the requested Product or transaction.

If you use sharing features of our Products, we will share your Personal Information as needed to perform the sharing functions you request. But we don't have any control over what the people, services, or third-party websites you've shared with do with your Personal Information after that.

We may respond to subpoenas, court orders, or legal process by disclosing your Personal Information and other related information, if necessary. We also may choose to establish or exercise our legal rights or defend against legal claims.

We may collect and possibly share Personal Information and any other additional information available to us in order to investigate, prevent, or take action regarding illegal activities, suspected fraud, situations involving potential threats to the physical safety of any person, violations of Eyefi's terms of service, or as otherwise required by law.

We will ask for your consent before we use or share your information for any purpose other than the reason you provided it or as otherwise provided by this policy. In order to let us know your preferences, we will require an action on your part, such as checking the appropriate option, to indicate your consent.

### Sharing profile information on OKDOTHIS:

  * Information you provide in your OKDOTHIS profile is accessible and searchable by other OKDOTHIS users. By using the OKDOTHIS application and entering information into your profile, you consent to the disclosure of such information to other users.
  * If you choose, you can use our locate other users with OKDOTHIS accounts either through (i) your contacts list, (ii) third-party social media sites or (iii) through a search of names and usernames on OKDOTHIS.
  * If you choose to find other users through your device's contacts list, then OKDOTHIS will access your contacts list to determine whether or not someone associated with your contact is using OKDOTHIS.
  * If you choose to find other users through a third-party social media site, then you will be prompted to set up a link to the third-party service and you understand that any information that such service may provide to us will be governed by this Privacy Policy.
  * If you choose to find other users through a search of names or usernames on OKDOTHIS then simply type a name to search and we will perform a search on our database of users.
  * We have functionality that allows you to invite someone to OKDOTHIS. In using this feature, you may select a person directly from the contacts list on your device and send a text or email from your personal account. You understand and agree that you are responsible for any charges that apply to communications sent from your device, and because this invitation is coming directly from your personal account, OKDOTHIS does not have access to or control this communication.

## Security of your Personal Information

Eyefi is committed to protecting the Personal Information you share with us. We utilize a combination of industry-standard security technologies, procedures, and organizational measures to help protect your Personal Information from unauthorized access, use or disclosure.

While we strive to protect your Personal Information, we cannot ensure the security of the information you transmit over the Internet. We recommend you to take every precaution in protecting your Personal Information when you are on the Internet. For example, do not use the same password for multiple web sites, change your passwords often, use a combination of letters and numbers when creating passwords, and make sure you use a secure browser.

## Linked websites and third party services

Our websites and services may provide links to other third-party websites and services, which are outside our control and not covered by this policy. We encourage you to review the privacy policies posted on these (and all) sites you visit or services you use.

## Children's privacy

Eyefi does not knowingly collect Personal Information from children under the age of 13. If we learn that we have collected Personal Information on a child under the age of 13, we will delete that data from our systems. Eyefi encourages parents and guardians to take steps to protect their children's on-line privacy. The Federal Trade Commission and other government agencies provide resources to help protect children's on-line privacy, including <http://www.onguardonline.gov/topics/protect-kids-online>.

## Consent to Transfer, Processing and Storage of Personal Information

Eyefi processes Personal Information on servers in the United States and other countries. In some cases, Eyefi may process or store your Personal Information on a server outside your own country, where laws regarding processing of Personal Information may be less stringent than the laws in your country. By providing your Personal Information you understand and consent to such transfer, processing and storage of Personal Information.

## Questions or comments?

Should you have any privacy-related questions or comments related to this privacy policy, please send an email to [privacy@eyefi.com](mailto:privacy@eyefi.com).

## Policy updates

Eyefi may amend this privacy statement from time to time, and at any time. We will post a notice whenever this privacy statement is materially changed. Your continued use of the Eyefi website or Products after any change will signify and confirm your assent to those changes.
